Frances Douglas papers, 1892-1963
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 5: Photographs, 1884 - 1960
  - Subseries 1: Frances Douglas, c. 1890 - 1960
    - Douglas, Frances - Tucson, with family, 1911 - 1916 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Douglas, Frances, 1911 - 1938 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Douglas, Frances - Tucson, c. 1920's (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Douglas, Frances, Stanford c. 1930's (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Douglas, Frances, 1930's (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Douglas, Frances - Tucson, c. 1890's - 1910 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Douglas, Frances - Childhood Home [nd] (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Douglas, Frances - Photograph plate [nd] (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 2: Family, Friends, and Associates, 1884 - 1954
    - Bacon, Louisa, [nd] (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Browne, Francis Fisher, [nd] (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Burgess, Lily (nurse to Jordan and Keith Lummis), 1904 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Chavez, Amado and daughter, [nd] (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - DeKalb, Courtenay, 1911 - 1931 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Dixon, Constance Maynard III, [nd] (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Douglas, Ambrose (brother), [nd] (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - BDouglass, Frederick O. (brother) and family, c. 1900 - 1954 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Douglas, Morrison D. (brother) and family, [nd] - 1930 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Dow, Annie Douglas Whitman and family, [nd] - 1938 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Family and friends at Isleta and El Alisal, 1892 - 1907 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Friends, misc., 1897 - 1934 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Hazard, John and Gibson (nephews of C. DeKalb), 1912 - 1931 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Hazeltine, Mr. and Mrs., 1927 and 1931 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Hearst, Phoebe, Hacienda, 1909 - 1910 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Hessey, Flossie Douglas (sister) and family, 1889 - 1949 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Jordan, Jessie Knight, Jordan, David Starr, and family, 1898 - 1938] (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Keeler, Charles, [nd - 1908] (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Lummis, Amado (son), [nd] (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Lummis, Amado and Turbes?son and daughter), 1894 - 1900 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Lummis, Jordan "Quimu" (son), 1900 - 1920 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Lummis, Jordan "Quimu" (son) and family, 1924 - 1947 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Lummis, Keith (son), 1904 - 1955 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Lummis, Keith (son) and family, 1932 - 1951 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Lummis, Turbesé (daughter), 1892 - c. 1916 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Lummis, Turbesé, Jordan and Keith (daughter and sons), 1901 - 1920 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Mitchell, Captain, 1899 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Moody, Charles A., [nd] (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Phillips, Dr. Albert W. and family, 1888 - 1927 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Rea, Alice Douglas (sister) and family, c. 1884 - 1957 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Spanish authors, [nd] (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: Trips, Mines and Residential Locations, 1889 - 1932
    - Isleta, New Mexico, 1889 - 1918 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - "Las Casitas", c. 1900 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Mexico, photographs and postcards, 1911 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - New Orleans, c. 1915 - 1930's (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Roadside Mine, 1923 - 1932, [nd] (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Spain, Burgos Cathedral, [nd] (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Spain and Morocco, trip for Department of Commerce, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Spain (1 of 2), photographs and postcards, 1919 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Spain (2 of 2), 1919 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Spain, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Tucson Home, c. 1912 (Box 24, Folder 8)